好了  拉杰
Okay, raj.
把6号螺丝刀递给我
Hand me the #6 torx screwdriver.
停
Stop.
不能这么做  这样不对
We can't do this. it's not right.
谢尔顿  你只有两个选择
Sheldon, you have two choices.
出城之前  要么换个大点的硬盘
Either you let him put a bigger hard drive in the tivo,
要么删掉一些数据
Or you delete stuff before we go out of town.
但是一旦开箱  保修单就作废了
But once you open the box, you've voided the warranty.
保修单可是
The warranty is a sacred covenant
我们和生产商之间的神圣契约
We've entered into with the manufacturer.
他提供设备的保障
He offers to stand by his equipment,
我们则保证不开箱
And we in return agree not to violate
亵渎内部硬件
The integrity of the internal hardware.
这张小贴纸就是辨别我们是否守法的标志
This little orange sticker is all that stands between us and anarchy.
行  那我们不碰硬件
Okay, then we won't touch the hard drive.
直接删除《太空堡垒》第1季
We'll just erase the first season of battlestar.
行了  我们违法吧
There. we're outlaws.
给  莱纳德  这个够大吗
Here you go, leonard. is this going to be big enough?
刚好
It's perfect.
给独角兽带水仙花差不多够了
For taking daffodils to your unicorn.
只是拿来装笔记本的
It's just for my notebooks.
谢谢  佩妮
Thanks, penny.
我好喜欢旧金山
I love san francisco.
真想和你们一起去
I wish I was going with you.
我很理解你会嫉妒
I understand your envy.
这是绝不能错过的研讨会
This is a can't-miss symposium.
在那儿会讨论
There are going to be discussions
生物细胞计算机元件
on bioorganic cellular computer devices,
多线程任务处理的优势
The advancements in multi-threaded task completion,
还有用非平衡格林函数解决
Plus a roundtable on the nonequilibrium green's function approach
原子内光化电离过程的圆桌会议呢
to the photoionization process in atoms.
我通常只去玩击锤和坐缆车
When I go, I usually just get hammered and ride the cable cars.
这次会议挺大型的
This conference is kind of a big thing.
由乔治·斯穆特做开场发言呢
The keynote address is being delivered by george smoot.
偶滴神啊  乔治·斯穆特
Oh, my god, the george smoot?
你听说过他吗
You've heard of him?
当然没有
Of course I haven't.
乔治·斯穆特是个物理学家  诺贝尔奖得主
George smoot is a nobel prize-winning physicist,
当代伟人之一
One of the great minds of our time.
他对黑体和宇宙微波背景辐射的
His work in black body form and anisotropy of the cosmic microwave
各向异性的研究 跟宇宙起源的观点有许多相通之处
Background radiation cemented our understanding of the origin of the universe.
名字挺搞笑的  斯穆特
It's kind of a funny name, though-- "smoot."
对牛牛弹琴
It's like talking to a chimp.
既然在这被羞辱了  就祝你们飞行愉快
Okay, now that I've been completely insulted, have a good flight.
我倒是想坐飞机呢
Yeah, I wish.
我们不坐飞机  坐火车
We're not flying. we're taking the train.
-挺酷的  -太苦了
- Oh, cool. - yeah, cool.
比坐飞机长7倍的时间  还贵2倍的价钱
Seven times as long as flying, and costs almost twice as much.
那干嘛坐火车
Well, then why are you doing it?
我们投过票
Well, we had a vote.
3个投坐飞机
Three of us voted for airplane.
但谢尔顿投坐火车
Sheldon voted for train.
所以只能坐火车
So we're taking the train.
别这么说嘛  莱纳德
Don't say it like that,Leonard.
这么说  我们可算能坐回火车咯O(∩_∩)O
Say it like "we're taking the train!"
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第17集
我们准备去苹果专卖店
We're all going over to the apple store
戏弄那些技术人员
To make fun of the guys at the genius bar.
你去吗
You want to come?
我很喜欢玩这个  但现在有点忙
Oh, I always enjoy that, but I'm a little busy.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我在简化打包行李的任务
I'm simplifying the task of packing for our trip.
瞧  给衣物贴上电子标签
See, by attaching rfid tags to my clothing,
就能用识别笔
It will enable my laptop
激活笔记本读取和鉴别它们
to read and identify the items with this wand.
然后我就能参照目的地
I will then cross-reference them against destination,
预先安排的活动幅度
Anticipated activity spectrum,
天气情况  旅行时长  等等来确定带什么去
weather conditions, duration of trip,Et cetera.
确实简化了不少
Well, that does sound much simpler.
你还要多长时间
How long is this going to take?
以现在的速度  3小时11分钟
Assuming I can keep up this pace, three hours, 11 minutes,
还要鉴于这次毫无意义的
And plus however long it takes
对话的时长
To conclude this fairly pointless conversation.
现在感觉戏弄苹果的技术人员有点多余
Wow. teasing the guys at the apple store seems a little redundant now.
我没听懂
I don't follow.
我也不想你听懂  一会见
I wouldn't expect you to. I'll see you later.
袜子一对  棉质  菱形花纹  蓝色
Sock, one pair, cotton, argyle, blue.
你们这是干嘛
What on earth are you doing?
不管是什么  看来都是错的
Whatever it is, I'm guessing we're doing it wrong.
先生们  这可是海岸星光号
Gentlemen, this is the coast starlight,
全美最好的火车之一
One of the great american trains
行驶在全美最经典线路之一
Operating on one of the classic american routes.
在这边
On this side,
可以看到全海景
You'll see panoramic ocean vistas
任何运输工具都无法做到这点
inaccessible to any other form of transportation,
而这边
while on your side,
你只能面对350英里上的好市多超市
you'll be treated to 350 miles of costcos,
捷飞络汽车服务店
jiffy lubes,
带凸地泳池的煤渣砖房子
and cinder block homes with above-ground pools.
走吧  拉杰
Come on, raj.
捷飞络有什么不好
What's wrong with jiffy lubes?
不对
No.
为什么
Why not?
超出轴距了
That's over the wheelbase.
你们对1980前期普式火车上
Are you completely unfamiliar with the suspension
超级豪华的 悬浮座椅一点都不知道吗
Characteristics of a pre-1980 pullman-built superliner deluxe passenger coach?
谢尔顿  我们上火车才90秒
Sheldon, we've been on this train 90 seconds,
你就说了几万个字
And you've already said a thousand words.
直接说坐哪  然后闭嘴
Just tell us where to sit and shut up.
这里
Here.
我希望你听着规律的车轮和铁轨的撞击声
I'm hoping once you reap the endorphic rewards of the steady
得到脑袋产生的安多芬犒劳后
Clickety-clack of steel wheels on polished rails,
焦躁能有所缓解
Your sour disposition will abate.
可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
与此同时  回到21世纪
Meanwhile, back in the 21st century,
人们也开始收托盘桌 支起座椅背
People are raising their tray tables and putting their seat-backs in an upright position
因为已经到旧金山了
'cause it's time to land in san francisco.
已经不错了
It's not so bad, really.
至少这种火车有现代管道系统
At least these trains have modern plumbing.
在印度
In india,
你只能蹲在车厢里的一个洞上面
You squat over a hole in the train and expose
把屁屁曝光在拉贾斯坦的冰冷空气中
and expose your naked buttocks to the chilly air of Rajasthan.
他这是个比喻
He is referring, of course,
比作乘坐印度铁路宏伟的千柱之庙特快的三等旅客
To third class on indian railways' magnificent ranakpur express and its
和从马哈拉施特拉邦到比卡内尔枢纽站 1200公里的旅程
1,200-kilometer journey from maharashtra to the bikaner junction.
看吧  他现在无聊到有够国际水准了
Oh, look, now he's boring on an international scale.
我靠  快看
Holy crap! look!
真的是她么  没可能吧
Is that who I think it is? it can't be.
萨默·格萝怎么会来坐火车的
What would summer glau be doing riding the train?
可能约翰·康纳上车了 她来保护他  对付屠魔侠
Maybe john connor's aboard and she's protecting him from an evil terminator.
不太像  那是电视剧  莱纳德
Unlikely. that's a television show, leonard.
谢了
Thank you.
当然  如果未来天网真的存在
Of course, if skynet actually did exist in the future,
侵入并毁灭人类最好的方法将会是将终结者送去
A perfect way to infiltrate and destroy  mankind would be
摆成在著名的电影电视中出演终结者的演员的造型
to send terminators back posing as actors who have played terminators in
让我们在臆想的安全感中苟且偷生
Popular films and television series, lulling us into a false sense
比如  那是终结者外传中的萨默·格萝
a false sense of security, i.e., "that's summer glau "from the sarah connor chronicles.
不  萨默  不要杀我 我真的是机器人
"no, summer, don't kill me! I'm pro-robot! ahh!"
至少他不再唠叨那些关于火车的废话了
At least he's off the train crap.
谢尔顿  我应该向你道歉
Sheldon, I owe you an apology.
坐上这辆火车是我一生中最幸运的事
Taking the train was a stroke of brilliance!
我居然有机会把到一个终结者
I've actually got a shot at a terminator.
拜托
Oh, please.
如果说到终结者
When it comes to terminators,
你也就能泡到阿诺德·施瓦辛格
You've got a better shot of scoring with arnold schwarzenegger.
你忽略了某件事
You're overlooking something.
我将与她在一个密闭的空间中共处11个小时
I have 11 hours with her in a confined space.
除非她愿意跳火车
Unless she's willing to jump off a moving train,
从山坡上滚下去
Tuck and roll down the side of a hill,
她终将屈服于霍华德·沃罗威茨的魔掌之下
She will eventually succumb to the acquired taste that is howard wolowitz.
我赌她会跳火车
My money's on tuck and roll.
我很困惑
I'm confused.
我以为你正身陷于
I thought you were involved in some sort of
与莱斯利·温克尔的亲密关系中
Socially intimate pairing with leslie winkle.
-谢尔顿  告诉你这是为什么吧  -好吧
Sheldon, let me explain to you how this works. all right.
-那是萨默·格萝  -所以呢
-That's summer glau. -yes.
就这样了
That's it.
慢着
Hang on a sec.
为什么让你先去泡她
Why do you get first crack at her?
有这样几个原因
Um, well, let's see, couple reasons.
第一  是我先看到她的
One, I saw her first.
不是你  是我
No, you didn't. I did.
好吧
Fair enough.
但是  让我说下原因二
But... then, let me move on to #2.
不像你  我不用喝醉也可以和女人交谈
Unlike you, I can actually talk to women when I'm sober.
你忘了一件事  我即使不说话也具有异国情调
You fail to take into account that even mute, I am foreign and exotic,
哪像你  又弱又白的
While you, on the other hand, are frail and pasty.
古语说的好  又弱又白不会挂
Well, you know the old saying, "pasty and frail never fail."
拜托  那我呢
Excuse me, but what about me?
为什么我就不能试试的
Why don't I get a shot?
好吧  去吧
Fine, go ahead.
去试试
Take a shot.
你知道
You know,
我已经有个泡不到的金发美女在家了
I've already got a gorgeous blonde back home that I can't score with.
我就让你们两个泡这个吧
I think I'll let you two take this one.
谢尔顿  火车上有没有卖酒的
Sheldon, is there a place on this train to get alcohol?
问得好
Interesting that you ask.
海岸星光号最近新增了重新装修的太平洋休闲车厢
The coast starlight recently added the refurbished pacific parlour car.
始建于1956年  最初叫做圣达菲上等车厢
Built in 1956 and originally known as the santa fe lounge car,
-下层是剧院 上层是酒吧  提供...  -行了  怎么走
The lower level is a theater and the upper  Level is a bar that offers -which way?
提供酒品  如果你一直坐到波特兰
Wine tastings if you're going as far as portland.
你到底去不去和她搭讪
So aren't you going to go talk to her?
我会去的  正在想开场白呢
I will, I'm just working on my opening line.
霍华德  她什么开场白没听过啊
She's probably heard every possible line, howard.
你简单地嗨一下不就行了
Why don't you just try "hello"?
不不不  那样会吓坏女孩子的
No, no, no, that always creeps girls out.
我得想点幽默的
I need to come up with something that's funny,
聪明又微妙地提示她
Smart and delicately suggests that my sexual
我的性禀赋和我的身高不成比例
Endowment is disproportionate to my physical stature.
我看你11个小时是想不出来了
You're going to need more than 11 hours.
-坏了  -怎么了
-Oh, no. -what's the matter?
-我忘带我的优盘了  -所以呢
-I forgot my flash drive. -so?
所以我们必须回去
So we have to go back.
谢尔顿  我会问你为什么
Okay, sheldon, I'm going to say "why"
但你不能回答因为我忘带我的优盘了
And your answer cannot be "because I forgot my flash drive."
你不明白
You don't understand.
我的优盘里有我的关于早期宇宙中
My flash drive has my paper on
M理论效应的天体物理学探索的论文
Astrophysical probes of m-theory effects in
我本来打算在会上
The early universe that I was going to
给乔治·斯穆特的
Give to george smoot at the conference.
你为什么要把你的论文给乔治·斯穆特
Why do you have to give your paper to george smoot?
写得太好了  他需要读一读
It's brilliant. he needs to read it.
你可以等咱们回来发邮件给他的嘛
So you'll send him an e-mail when we get back.
那我就看不到他读我论文时两眼放光的表情啦
Then I won't get to see his face light up as he reads it.
当然了
Right. of course.
真是糟糕透顶
Oh, this is an unmitigated disaster.
事已至此  无力回天  您就歇会吧
Well, there's nothing you can do about it, so relax.
向后靠 迷醉在车轮与锃亮的铁轨撞击的咔哒咔哒声中
Sit back, enjoy the clickety-clack of the steel wheels on the polished rails.
你忘带了优盘...
You forgot your flash drive...
忍十个小时55分钟就好
Only ten hours, 55 minutes to go.
这里真热啊[真性感啊]
It's hot in here.
一定到夏天了[一定是萨默]
Must be summer.
那么 美眉们去哪啊
So... Where you gals headed?
我想出完美的解决办法了
Okay, I've found the perfect solution.
我们在下一站奥克斯纳德下车
We get off the train at the next stop in oxnard.
然后乘坐1:13的火车返回联合车站
We then take the 1:13 train back to union station.
打车回公寓  拿上我的优盘
We take a cab back to the apartment, get my flash drive,
冲向圣路易斯奥比斯波
And then race to san luis obispo, where,
假设一路绿灯路上无人  我们就能赶上火车
Assuming the lights are with us and minimal traffic, we'll meet the train.
我有个更好的主意
I've got a better idea.
你又想讽刺我
Are you going to be sarcastic?
孩子  你把我的乐趣都剥夺了
Boy, you take all the fun out of it for me.
看  佩妮在家呢
Look, penny's home.
为什么不打给她  让她去我们家
Why don't we just call her, have her go in the apartment,
把你优盘里的论文发到你邮箱里呢
Get your flash drive and e-mail you the paper?
-但是优盘在我那个上锁的抽屉里  -所以呢
But the flash drive is in a locked drawer in my desk. so?
钥匙藏在我的房间里
The key is hidden in my room.
-所以呢  -佩妮需要进去我的房间
So? penny would have to go into my room.
-所以呢  -没有人可以进我房间
So? people don't go in my room!
我懂了
I see.
看来你又一次陷入了进退两难的境地
Well, it seems once again, you're caught between a rock and a crazy place.
真讨厌这种感觉
Oh, I hate when that happens.
这儿真热
It's hot in here.
现在肯定是夏天
It must be summer.
这儿真热
It's hot in here.
肯定是夏天
Must be summer.
这儿真热  肯定是夏天
It's hot in here. must be summer.
这儿真热
It's hot in here.
肯定是夏天
Must be summer.
-这种说法真有趣  -真的
That's cute. really?
是我编的
I just made it up.
你看过贫民窟的百万富翁了没
Have you seen slumdog millionaire?
看过了  我太喜欢了
Oh, yeah, I loved it.
某种程度来说它是以我为原型来写的
It's loosely based on my life.
嗯
Yeah,
我们准备把表演放在某个晚上  在一个99座的剧院里
We're putting the play on for one night in this little 99-seat theater.
你能来吗
Can you come?
太好了
Oh, great.
你知道还有哪98人会想来吗
Do you know 98 other people that might want to come?
噢  别挂
Oh, hang on.
喂
Hello?
听仔细了
Listen carefully.
我现在会给你一系列指示
I'm about to give you a set of instructions,
你照着我说的一步步做
Which you must follow to the letter.
等会儿
Just a sec.
剧场是建在一个保龄球馆上面的  可能有点吵
The theater is above a bowling alley, so it's a little noisy,
但这可能是我唯一一次扮演
But it might be the only chance I'll ever get
安妮·弗兰克的机会[安妮日记主人公]
to play anne frank.
而且那个导演太聪明了
And the director is brilliant.
他利用打保龄球的声音  当作是纳粹的炮火声
He uses the bowling sounds as, like, nazi artillery.
好的  到时候见
Okay, great, I'll see you then.
喂
Hello?
第四步
Okay, step four.
你看到我化妆台上的塑料小盒吗
Do you see that small plastic case on my dresser?
你的化妆台?  你是哪位?
Your dresser? who is this?
我是谢尔顿
It's sheldon.
噢  好啊  谢尔顿
Oh, hey, sheldon!
旧金山怎么样
How is san francisco?
我没在旧金山
I'm not in san francisco.
我在火车上
I'm on a train.
你到底有没有在听我说话
Were you even listening to me?
没有  我在跟朋友聊天  怎么了
Uh, no, I was talking to my friend, but what's up?
怎么了  我来告诉你怎么了
What's up? I'll tell you what's up.
我现在性命交关
I'm in a crisis situation,
我现在要你集中所有小宇宙
And I need you to marshal your powers of concentration,
专心致志地...
Limited as they may be...
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
佩妮  我是莱纳德
Hi, penny. it's leonard.
嘿  莱纳德
Hey, leonard.
奇怪博士怎么了
What's going on with dr. wackadoodle?
他打来让你帮个忙的
He's calling to ask you a favor.
你肯定很奇怪  因为他没用佩妮  谢尔顿
You might be confused because he didn't use the words, "penny," "sheldon,
请  帮忙这几个词
" "please" or "favor."
好了
Okay.
闲聊得够了
Enough chitchat.
听好  第一步
Okay, step one.
找到我们房子的备用钥匙
Locate your emergency key to our apartment.
第二步  走进我们的房子
Step two, enter our apartment.
第三步...
Step three...
走进我的房间
Enter my bedroom.
第四步...
Step four...
等等  谢尔顿  又有电话来了
Oh, hang on, sheldon, getting another call.
别挂
No!
莱纳德  我告诉你
Leonard, let me tell you something.
我太期待个人机器人助理的诞生了
Personal robots cannot get here soon enough.
那颗明亮的小星早早的就偷偷探出她的头
And that bright little star peeking her head out early today...
那就是金星
That's venus.
太赞了
That is so cool.
你对太空知道得真多
You really know a lot about space.
拜托
Come on.
你演电视剧萤火虫的时候  你可真的是在太空里啊
When you were on tv in firefly, you were actually in space.
你不会是那种真的相信那些是真的人吧
You're not one of those guys who really believe that, are you?
你说那些没希望的怪人吗
You mean one of the hopeless geeks?
当然不是
No.
他们都是疯子
Those are crazy people.
霍华德  做做好人  帮我再拿一瓶
Howard, be a dear and get me another one of these.
告诉你  他就是那种白痴
Now, him, he's one of those geeks.
听着  在无第二方监视的情况下进入我房间之前
All right, now, before you enter my bedroom unescorted,
我需要你明白这种一次性的
I need you to understand that this onetime
通行权并不能转换为永久性的
Grant of access does not create a permanent easement.
通行权
Easement.
是一种准许进入的法定权利
It's a legal right of access.
老天她真无知
Good grief.
什么
What?
不行  别让我等着
No, don't put me on hold.
噢
Oh!
你敢相信吗
Do you believe him?
平时跟女人在一起  他就像个人形熟土豆
Normally around women, he has the personality of a boiled potato.
喝了一瓶啤酒  他就成了把妹高手了
Put one beer in him, and he's m. night charmalarmalon.
这是他喝的吗
Is that what he's drinking?
这都不是真的啤酒
It's not even real beer.
-什么  -看这里
What? look at it.
无酒精啤酒
"non-alcoholic beer."
怎么回事
What's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
我猜是某种安慰剂效应
Some sort of placebo effect, I guess.
你说安慰剂
Placebo, you say.
有趣了
Interesting.
嗯  我还在  我还能去哪儿  我可是在火车上啊
Yes, I'm still here. where am I going? I'm on a train.
现在
Now,
你要找的是一个小型木制盒子
What you'll be looking for is a small wooden box located
放在霍伯曼球面和嵌着黄铜矿的石英样本中间
Between a hoberman's sphere and a sample of quartz flecked with pyrite.
是霍伯曼球面
Hoberman's sphere.
就是一个可收缩的二十面球体
It's collapsible icosidodecahedron.
不  那个有时间的东西是我的闹钟
No, the thing with the time on it is my alarm clock.
其实  在印度有不同的星座名字
Actually, in india, the names of constellations are different.
你们有北斗七星  我们则有咖喱大锅
Where you have the big dipper, we have the big curry pot.
那是你胡编的
You're making that up.
被你揭穿了
You got me.
那你准备怎么惩罚我?
Now what are you going to do with me?
-拉杰  -什么事?
Raj. yes?
-看啊  -这是什么?
Look. what am I looking at?
你说呢
You tell me.
无酒精啤酒
"non-alcoholic beer."
嗨  我就是别人常说的小身材大智慧
Hi. I'm the small package good things come in.
好吧  我是找到一个盒子  但里面只有信没有钥匙
Okay, I got a box, but there's no key in here. just letters.
不是那个盒子  放回去
That's the wrong box. put it back.
谢尔顿  这是你奶奶寄来的信吗?
Oh, sheldon, are these letters from your grandmother?
别看那些信!
Don't read those letters!
看呀  她管你叫小甜派
Oh, look, she calls you "moon pie."
好可爱啊
That is so cute.
不准看信!
Put down the letters!
嗨  佩妮  我是莱纳德
Hey, penny. it's leonard.
嗨  莱纳德  坐火车感觉如何?
Hey, leonard. how's the train ride?
相当愉快
Delightful.
听着  我不知你现在干嘛
Listen, I don't know what you're doing right now,
但谢尔顿稍稍有些咬牙切齿了
But there are little bubbles forming on the corners of sheldon's mouth.
好吧  我是有点过火了
Okay, yeah, I kind of crossed a line.
让他接吧
Put him back on.
谢谢哦
Thank you.
我回来了
I'm back.
怎么啦  小甜派?
What up, moon pie?
只有我奶奶才这么叫我!
Nobody calls me moon pie but meemaw!
嗨  佩妮  又是我莱纳德
Hey, penny. leonard again.
不管怎样  在梦里  我们两个在滑冰  二人世界
So anyway, in the dream, you and I were ice skating, just the two of us.
然后
And then,
我抬起你的脚踝  带着你
I picked you up by your ankles and twirled
转了一圈又一圈  直到你的腿都掉下来了
You round and round until your legs tore off.
我试着把它们粘回去  不过在那之前
I tried to stick them back on, but before I could,
你已变身成一只巨大的黑面包
You turned into a giant loaf of pumpernickel bread.
你知道是什么意思吗?
What do you think that means?
我真不知道
I really don't know.
我给你点提示吧
I'll give you a little clue.
我最爱的三明治?
My favorite sandwich?
黑面包加色拉米香肠[意大利蒜味香肠]
Salami on pumpernickel.
就这样?
Is that so?
你知道黑面包这个词吗?
And did you know the word "pumpernickel"
是从德语的抽水机和分币两个词演变来的
Comes from the german words "pumper" and "nickel,"
一不小心就会理解成放屁的小妖精了
Which loosely translates to "fart goblin"?
不  我不知道
No. I didn't.
好吧  我找到盒子了  接下来?
Okay, I found the box. now what?
你正拿着一个日本迷箱
You're holding a japanese puzzle box,
要打开它必须采取十个精确步骤
Which takes ten precise moves to open.
首先
First,
找到有钻石图案的镶板
Locate the panel with the diamond pattern and
然后将中间部分往左滑一毫米
Slide the center portion one millimeter to the left.
接着  在盒子的反面
Then, on the opposite end of the box,
将整个镶板往下推2毫米
Slide the entire panel down two millimeters.
你会听到一下轻轻的咔哒声
You'll hear a slight click.
等下  谢尔顿  你对这个盒子有什么情结吗?
Hang on. sheldon, do you have any emotional attachment to this box?
不  在网上买的便宜新奇货而已
No, it's a novelty I ordered off the internet.
你听到咔哒声了吗?
Did you hear the click?
还没
Not yet.
听到了
There it is.
好吧  换个话题
Okay, here's another one.
如果你嫁给了著名摇滚吉他手强尼·温特
If you married the famous rock guitarist johnny winter,
你的名字就冬夏皆有了
You'd be summer winter.
-唔唔  -是啊
Uh-huh. yep.
我这么拼死拼活就是想说  我喜欢你
Okay, I'm going to just go for broke here and say I like you.
是吗?
Yeah?
老实说  你觉得有什么话题
Do you realistically see any conversational path that would take me from
能改善下我们目前的窘况
Where we are right now to a place
以便你能答应我约你出去呢?
Where I could ask you out and you'd say yes?
没有
No.
很好
Fair enough.
我不会烦你了
I'll leave you in peace.
感激不尽
Thank you.
但我走之前
But before I go,
你介意我们拍张合照吗?
Would you mind if I just take one
我要贴在我的Fackbook上
Picture of us together for my facebook page?
当然不了
Sure.
好了  太棒了
Okay. great.
那个  我能拍张让我们看起来像在热吻吗?
Now, can I take one where it looks like we're making out?
好吧  现在你要把优盘插进USB接口...
Okay, now you're going to insert the flash drive into the usb port...
她之所以叫我小甜派
She calls me moon pie because I'm
是因为我看起来很可口  她想要一口吃掉
Nummy-nummy and she could just eat me up.
现在  拜托你快把优盘插进USB接口
Now, please put the flash drive in the usb port.
就是那个看起来像小鸭子嘴的东西
The one that looks like a little duck's mouth.
进展如何?
Hey, how'd it go?
终结者毁了我的手机
Terminator broke my phone.
失陪
Excuse me.
让我开诚布公吧
Okay, I'll be honest with you.
我花了两小时构思了各种搭讪方案
I've just spent the last two hours imagining various scenarios in my head,
就为了能给你留下个好印象
Trying to come up with some clever line to say to you.
但我最终意识到  我们都是人类
But then I finally realized you're a human being; I'm a human being.
我只要对你说...
I could just say to you...
下一站  圣巴巴拉市
Santa barbara.
抱歉  我要下车了
I'm sorry. this is me.
你好  我叫莱纳德
Hi, my name's leonard.
我是这样想的  你三年前获得诺贝尔奖
So, I'm thinking, you won the nobel prize what, three years ago?
你一定很烦  关于你近来有什么成就的言论
So you must deal with a whole lot of "what has smoot done lately?"
所以我们可以合作继续我的研究
My thought is we continue my research as a team-- you know, cooper-smoot,
按字幕顺序  可以起名叫库珀-斯穆特
you know, cooper-smoot, alphabetical--
我们就能赢得诺贝尔奖  你又重新登顶
and when we win the nobel prize, you'll be back on top.
尊敬的库珀博士  你疯了吗?
With all due respect, dr. cooper, are you on crack?
那就叫斯穆特-库珀好了!
Fine! smoot-cooper.